logogarden.com 2015-06-08

# LogoGarden - Privacy Policy

LogoGarden.com, Inc. respects your privacy This Privacy Statement informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. This statement is readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every LogoGarden.com Web page.

LogoGarden.com Inc. privacy practices are aimed to be consistent with U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor principles: Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Access and Accuracy, Security, and Oversight/Enforcement. More information about the U.S. Department of Commerce Safe Harbor Program can be found at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to set up solutions or purchase website marketing services, respond to requests that you make, to process transactions, to facilitate your request for a quote from a third party service provider or to aid us in serving you better. We may share your Personal Information with other businesses to offer you products, services, and promotions. In addition, we may share your Personal Information with other businesses that may contact you regarding requests for service. We may also use your Personal Information to provide you with electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails as well as information and offers about our products and services.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact LogoGarden.com, Inc. using the contact information at the end of this statement.

### How LogoGarden.com, Inc. uses automatic data collection tools:

  * Cookies
  * Web beacons
  * Embedded web links
  * LogoGarden.com, Inc. ads on third party websites
  * Information gathering tools

### Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

LogoGarden is a global organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders. This Privacy Statement applies to all LogoGarden.com, Inc.-owned websites and domains.

### Links to non-LogoGarden.com, Inc. websites

The LogoGarden.com, Inc. website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the LogoGarden.com website. LogoGarden.com, Inc. does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from LogoGarden.com, Inc. practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the LogoGarden.com, Inc. Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.

### Collection of personal information

To serve you better and understand your needs and interests, LogoGarden.com, Inc. collects, exports, and uses personal information with adequate notice and consent, along with required filings with data protection authorities, when applicable. For example, when you order products or services, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials.

In addition to the information you provide, LogoGarden.com, Inc. may also collect information during your visit to an LogoGarden.com website through our Automatic Data Collection Tools, which include Web beacons, cookies, embedded Web links, and other commonly used information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived at an LogoGarden.com, Inc. website. They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, clickstream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with LogoGarden.com, Inc. websites) and product information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers use IP addresses to communicate on the Internet, allowing users to browse and shop. LogoGarden.com, Inc. may also use some of these Automatic Data Collection Tools in connection with certain emails sent from LogoGarden.com, Inc. and therefore may collect information using these tools when you open the email or click on a link contained in the email.

### How we use your information

The information LogoGarden.com, Inc. collects to understand your needs and interests helps LogoGarden.com, Inc. deliver a consistent and personalized experience. For example, LogoGarden.com, Inc. may use your information to

  * assist you in completing a transaction or order;
  * communicate with you about products and services;
  * provide service and support;
  * update you on new services and benefits;
  * provide personalized promotional offers;
  * select content to be communicated to you;
  * allow you to participate in contests and surveys; and
  * contact you for market research regarding LogoGarden.com, Inc. products or services.

Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention.

### How we share your information

LogoGarden.com, Inc. shares personal information in the following ways:

  * LogoGarden.com, Inc. retains service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions and to assist LogoGarden.com, Inc. with marketing and communication initiatives. These providers and suppliers include, for example, credit card processors, providers of customer support and live-help, email service providers, automated data processors, and shipping agents. Suppliers and service providers are required by contract to keep confidential the information received on behalf of LogoGarden.com, Inc. and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for LogoGarden.com, Inc..
  * From time to time, LogoGarden.com, Inc. participates in marketing initiatives with other companies. As part of these initiatives, certain LogoGarden.com, Inc. services, such as printing of business cards, and marketing communications are delivered at the same time as those from other companies. Some of these services and communications offer you the option to share personal information with both LogoGarden.com, Inc. and the other companies participating in these initiatives. For example, you may receive marketing communications from LogoGarden.com, Inc. and other companies or have the opportunity to register online for software products from multiple companies. If you choose to provide personal information only to LogoGarden.com, Inc., LogoGarden.com, Inc. will not share this information with the other companies participating in that marketing initiative. If you choose to provide personal information to the other companies, that personal information will be handled according to the privacy policy of those companies. Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, LogoGarden.com, Inc. decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is LogoGarden.com, Inc.’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

### Children's privacy

LogoGarden.com, Inc. does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18 and does not target its websites to children under 18. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.

### Your choices and selecting your privacy preferences

#### Subscription communications

Subscription communications include email newsletters, articles, etc. that may be expressly requested by you or which you consented to receive. After you request such communications, you may opt out of receiving them by using one of the following methods:

  * Select the email "opt out" or "unsubscribe" link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each subscription communication.
  * Write to the LogoGarden.com, Inc. Privacy Office. Be sure to provide your name, email and postal address, and specific relevant information about the LogoGarden.com, Inc. subscriptions that you no longer wish to receive.

Please be aware that when you opt out of receiving certain subscription communications, it may affect the services you have chosen to receive from LogoGarden.com, Inc. where accepting the communications is a condition of receiving the services.

#### Access to and accuracy of your information

LogoGarden.com, Inc. strives to keep your personal information accurately recorded. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to help maintain data accuracy. LogoGarden.com, Inc. provides individuals with reasonable access to personal information that they provided to LogoGarden.com, Inc. and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for anonymization, blockage, or deletion, as applicable. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data.

#### Keeping your personal information secure

LogoGarden.com, Inc. takes seriously the trust you place in us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, LogoGarden.com, Inc. utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

When collecting or transferring sensitive information such as credit card information we use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The personal information you provide us is stored on computer systems located in controlled facilities which have limited access. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as credit card number or password) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payments and are not used for other purposes. As part of real-time payment processing, LogoGarden.com, Inc. subscribes to a fraud management service. This service gives you and LogoGarden.com, Inc. an extra level of security to guard against credit card fraud and to protect your financial data.

### Changes to this statement

If we change our privacy statement, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our statement, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.

### Contacting us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy statement, please send them to the Service@LogoGarden.com or write to us at the following address:

**LogoGarden Inc.**  
1620 Westgate Circle  
Suite 120  
Brentwood, TN 37027
